Applause for Ana Channel
What are you doing today?
Ana has been very busy lately.
I'm worried that you're not getting enough sleep.
I'd like to take you on a tour of the Timingz today.
Thank you very much.
And our guest this time is this gentleman.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
It's nice to have you here all the time.
It's nice to hear that, isn't it?
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm wearing it.
My voice is a little bit like Tom Brown's.
It's like he did this to my head.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We're the two Emmasos.
Thank you very much.
This is Ana and I...
This is my second or third time here.
Third time.
First time.
I love you, Ana.
I mean, we do karaoke together, and...
Gage-ge-ge-roo.
I'm so happy.
Gage-ge-ge-ro
I'm so happy, because I've always loved you, too.
Really?
It's not so bad.
It's not bad.I don't think it's that bad.
I have that impression.
On the other hand, who's the busy guy?
I'm curious.
I see you've come up with that term.
It's not bad.
Oh, it's the Minami tour.
We're going to take advantage of the opportunity.
Can I find my favorite merchandise?
Let's go.
Suddenly I'm in charge.
You're a surprise guest, aren't you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I appreciate it.
I'm sorry, sir, but I have to say...
This is where we sell pajamas.
Yes, of course.
Pajamas is one word for it.
But we have a different kind of pajamas.
They are generally called recovery wear.
It is generally called "recovery wear".
Do you know it?
Cute!
Yes, sir.
There's a way to ask that.
Just say, "I don't know.
Yes, I do.
We're developing recovery wear called Makune.
We're kneading ore into the threads.
It's designed to promote blood circulation throughout the body.
Simply put
Just by wearing these pajamas, you can alleviate fatigue.
These pajamas are designed to reduce fatigue just by wearing them.
What is kneaded into them?
That's legal, isn't it?
It's all a lie.It's all lies.
It's all a lie.
How can it be a lie?
It's supposed to increase blood circulation and reduce fatigue.
To reduce stiffness in the body...
It's an item that's supposed to have that effect.
How does it feel to the touch?
It's just around the corner.
Like a basketball uniform.
You see them all the time.
We are developing a variety of materials.
This one here is made of a dry material.
It's the kind of material that dries quickly after you sweat.
These are items with a smooth feel.
It's true that they are a bit transparent.
It doesn't look too hot.
That's right.
Looks cool.
It's been so hot that even at night the temperature hasn't dropped.
I've been putting the air conditioner on a timer.
I was using a fan to keep it cool.
I've heard that many people are turning on the air conditioner all night long
so I've heard.
I see.
So the need for long sleeves has been rising.
I think the need for long sleeves has been rising.
What kind of clothes do you wear, Anu?
I wear checks.
Plaid.
I like the ones at Shimamura.
Heh.
That's all I wear.
You don't look like you check.
Sorry about the checks.
Can I have a piece of elastic?
I'll have to get some checks.I'll have to prepare a check.
I'll see what I can do.
Do you have a pen or something?
I don't have a pen.
I'll have to do something to cover the check.
Check.
I'm sure you'll need a check.
You're right.
I can't do a monologue.
Check-related?
It's all about the check.
I mean...
A repertoire of impersonations?
I have a repertoire of impersonations.
Checkers
Then, I will play Checkers.
Checkers.
Please don't let them forgive me.
I've never been forgiven.
I'm going to fall over.
From now on, I really do.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I like the ones with the ribs.
I've got one with an embroidery.
I like the ones with the frills.
They're cute, aren't they?
Yeah, they're cute.
I have one with an embellishment.
Yes, we do.
I should have come here sooner.
It's nice with an edge.
It's nice, isn't it?
It's cute.They're so cute.
It feels like pajamas, doesn't it?
It's like...
They're cute.
What are you two wearing?
I have the smooth ones.
They're really hot.
I'm wearing a paten.
People decide what's sexy and what's not.
What do you wear?
I don't wear pajamas or anything.
I just wear shorts and a T-shirt.
I might wear pajamas every now and then.
Pajamas.
What do you think? Something I can try on.
Something with a soft material would be nice.
Let's try them on.
Now then, since it looks like you've finished changing, let's get you out of here.
They're so good, I'll give them to you.
They're so light that I don't even feel them on! They fit me perfectly, but you know... the back pivots, too.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a good pair of pajamas that will fit you.
I think it's good, don't you?
I mentioned earlier that it's a recovery wear, so it's supposed to promote recovery and reduce fatigue.
I'm sure it's all part of the process.
It's also a good idea to take it with you on tours and such.
There are many people who use it in that way, and also athletes who overwork their bodies use it a lot.
How much is this?
22,000 yen. But on this day, if I say I saw that channel...
Did I mention that?
When Mr. Sano called in, it was like he was calling in a comedian.
It was very painful.
I did it by myself and it was so embarrassing because I felt like Hamada-san.
I didn't try to pull it off, but this is the only kind I know.
Maybe it's because I have a high intuition, but my voice is distant.
Lower, please.Low, please.
You have a high intuition, don't you, Mr. Hamada?
The results are in!
Next, let's invite Yasuno-chan.
What was it?
Murakami chose bakunemesh.
Murakami chose Bakunemesh.
Let's have him come out. Please come out.
Bakunemesh!
It's not the name of a special move.
It's Bakunemesh!
What do you think?
Very nice.
No waste, I knew it.
I've been exercising.
I did.
This is the Bakunemesh series, which stretches up and down, left to right.
The feature is that it doesn't feel tight at all when you sleep.
The armholes here, at the shoulders, are quite loose in pattern.
It is true that the length of the garment would be a little longer than this, but it is not tight.
Oh, a little here.Over here.
Then, let's just show the width.
How wide is it?
Give me a break.
It's a pretty one.
It's nice.
Then this guy!
KANO chose
It's a back net line ladies!
KANO, here you go!
What the hell?
Hey!
Mr. KANO!
What's with the bakune?What the hell is he doing?
You've got a bakune!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry.
Even your eyes are red.
You're blushing.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, this is great! Oh, my God, it's so good.
Look at this.
Pink, pink, pink.
Pink.
As the name "ladies" implies...
It's designed to make women's body lines look a little more flattering.
It's made to be comfortable to wear.
This is also a jacket for a 3 piece band, right?
What do you think?
It will sell a million copies.
What is the name of the band?
Baxue.
Baksue.Yes, I think so.
We called ourselves Bakunee.
It's Baxue.
I'm sorry, bakune was rejected.
Baksue.
That's great.
I thought it was a little bit...
What?
I thought it was just for sleeping, but it's so comfortable.
It's really nice, isn't it?
How much are these things? Ours.
The mesh.
The mesh one.
It's 22,000 yen.
Twenty-two thousand yen.22,000 yen is
is
that channel
That channel
I saw that channel...
20,000
10 yen?
No, no, no.
10% off.
15% off.
Are you sure?
I'll do it for you.
Oh, my God.
It's big.
I'm so happy.
I hope you'll all bakune to the big one.
15% off!
I saw that channel!
I'll let you do that.
That's great.
What if I tell you I saw it but it wasn't heavy?
No discount.If you don't say it was interesting, I'll just say...
You had to say it was interesting.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please.
That channel.
Now we come to the main attraction of the day.
This is Mr. Tempio.
Wasn't that the main place?
No, of course the bajamas are important.
But the appetizer, or in the case of fried food, the batter is still on the top.
I guess it just didn't hit the spot.
I'm sorry.My apologies.
We were going to look for a pillow to help Ano sleep better.
Well, let's get to it.
Shall we go look for a pillow?
Ano wants to find a good pillow.
What kind of heat do you usually use?
Certainly.
On my face.
Face down?
Face down.
We have a pillow that is suitable for lying on your face.
I'd be happy to show you.
No, it's not.
It's in the back.
This one?
Yes.
It's cute.
It's shaped like this.
It's a very special shape.
It's also called a "universal pillow".
It easily fits all thermal properties, from prone to prone, from side to side, and from back to back.
Wow.
Would you like to try it?
It's a little bit like sleeping.By all means.
One time.
What's this for?
You can leave your shoes on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If you could put your hand between those shoes...
It'll feel good.
How's that?
That feels good.
That feels so good.
It's like we're in love.It's like I'm involved.
It's folded in.
I see. And here, around the chest.
It's not too tight here.
This chest area is not painful.
Thank you very much.
But it looks like there's no cover.
Please marry me.
We were both doing mail order.
But it looks like there's no cover.
Don't worry.
I didn't have a choice.
There's a cover.
We have a cover for you.
This one...
There's a slanted one.
What kind of shoulder is this for?
For those who want to support the neck well.
This series is recommended for people who often sleep on their backs and sides.
I don't know if I have trouble sleeping on my back or on my side.
Let's have you lie on your back for a while.
I didn't like the idea of lying on my back.
So let's try it on your back.
Sure.
That's about right.
This one's better.This one goes right along the neck.
Are you catching up?
I'm catching up.
He's so cute.
You're so cute.
You should put out a book of pictures of you tied up in bed.
I'll do it.
This might be good.
This is really good.
I think she wants to hold him.You want to hold him, don't you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sleep with this.
I'm feeling a little uncomfortable here.
I feel uncomfortable.
If only there was a pillow.
You have a pillow?
Why don't you hold it?
That's a good idea.
I always hug my futon.
I can't sleep without it.
If you have back pain and want to keep sleeping on your side...
I like this.
Let me see. Turn around.
It's really good.
It's so good! This one's really good, too.
This cut here is good, too. It's so good!
I want to take a picture of this angle and spread it around to my fans.
It's so good!
Hey, Leah!
She's so cute!
Looks like it's easy to sleep. I like it here.
I like how she's not really sleeping, but sleep and anochan look good together.
Her sleeping face is so cute.
Wow, it's really nice.I think it's taken this close.
What's the difference between these, the ones with the different patterns?
It's a premium model of the one you just tried.
It's a little longer and wider.
They're definitely bigger.
It's a pillow with an added feature called "Smart Cool" that keeps the pillows from crowding.
I see.
With this screen. Oops.
I don't need that reality.
How's that type of thing, the wrap-around type?That's the type. The type that wraps around you. How's that?
It's so much better.
Oh, no.
You were so cute earlier.
What's the difference?
The quality of the screen.
I think it's the way she sleeps. I want her to sleep more like Sleeping Beauty.
I'm not even holding her.
I really like that you can put the feet on the screen.
And this...
What do you think, McClure?
It's perfect.
Thank you very much.
It fits perfectly, doesn't it?
You're right, sir.
Everyone thinks it was probably made for them.
You made it for us, didn't you?
No, sir.
That's right.
That's too gay.
But it's big.
Is there a cover?
Don't worry.
We've got you covered.
You'll do it.
There's another one.
That's weird. I want the big one.
And do you have any other recommendations for McClure's?We have a popular series for the side.
It's called the "you pillow".
But I don't think it's meant to be in the same position the whole time you're sleeping.
It's kind of blue, isn't it?
It's for blue.
Oh, that's great.
It really fits my shoulder here.
Yes, just as you said.Yes, sir, just as you said.
Something doesn't seem to be working.
I mean, this thumbnail isn't bad, but...
He talks a lot in his sleep.
He talks like he's rambling the whole time.
He's so scary.
I've lived with him.
I've always said that Neptune is the most balanced of the trio.
Are you awake? I'm like...
Don't talk.
Okay, okay.
Oh, my God, this is so good.
You said it's for blue.
It's for blue.
This is a popular series around here.
What's this one?
It's a little expensive.
The previous model has a collar.
The neck can be supported by the collar.
I wish we could have brought this out.
Wait a minute.
It's hard to sleep.
Ready? Ready?
Oh, my God, that's high!
That's a high start.
But it's gonna fit, right?
Oh, yeah.Thank you very much.
You want to go this far?
Thank you for letting me go.
We're good to go.
Oh, wait a minute.
This is...
I'm pretty sure that's not even covered.
Not this one.
There's definitely no cover for this kind of management.There's no way I'd ever cover something like this for a business owner.
We just made it.
We're ready for you, sir.
Good.
I'm glad.
Here you go.
Thank you for saving it.
It's my pleasure.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for taking care of me
Here you go, Aro. Here.
You can go.
This one's good.
I'm sorry if it's lower.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Same pattern?
Same pattern, just a little lower.
I'm sorry, I just liked it higher.
If it's not what you want...
Go ahead.
Wow, this is it.
Who has this?
I love it.
You got it?
It's here.I still want to sleep on blue losses, so from now on...
I like this one.
It's fixed.
It fits.
It fits me.
By sinking down, you'll try to sleep in the right position.
By sinking in.By sinking down
It feels like you can sleep in a good position, doesn't it?
I like it.
You said it.
That's good.
That's nice.
Thank you very much.
I'm in.
Can I borrow the expensive one?
Yes, the expensive one.
I'll take the expensive one.
And the expensive one.
Please.
Here you go.
They're the same size, right? The width is the same, only the height. How's it look? No?
This one's good, too. Maybe this one. Maybe this one's good. This one's better.
It's more secure, right? I want to be more fixed and tied up, you know.
Wait, wait. You just said something. What did you just say? I want to be tied down. I don't know what "I want to be tied up.
Oh, that's good. I like the feeling of not having to move. Are these each one of those? Are the prices about the same?
The price goes up a little bit if you go up a little bit in volume, depending on the height.
I see. The density. You are right.
How much is this best one? How much is this one?
This one costs 22,000 yen. Twenty-two thousand yen.
Wow. That's amazing. Which one is the most popular?
The most popular series is this one. Oh, I see.
Also, the Original Neck Pillow is a popular series.
What's the difference? What's the difference? Height?
Just the height. If you sleep on your side, it is a matter of personal opinion, but according to our customers, we recommend this one if you sleep on your side,
The one with the neckline tends to be preferred by blue-faced sleepers.
I see. I see.
We also recommend pillows, but we deal in bedding in general,
We also have futons and mattresses available, so please just come and try them out.
Wow, may I? We'd be happy if you could try our bedding and mattresses.
Oh, you wrote that. The hardness.
Yes, it is. It's true.
Slightly hard.Slightly firm.
We have a NASA-certified mattress pillow brand, as is the case with the pillow I mentioned earlier.
NASA?
Yes. The material used in the rocket manufacturing process was developed into bedding in order to alleviate the G-force of gravity.
It is essential for the body when it is under load, even if only a little.
I see.
We can actually conduct an experiment to see how shock-absorbent the mattress is.
If it is a normal bed, it will probably get entangled.
I'm sure they will get entangled.
Please jump, jump, jump, jump.
What do you mean? What do you mean?
Oh!
Oh, my God!
It's already absorbing the shock.
Oh, my gosh! Wow!
Wow!
This is great!
Oh, my God!
I'm not involved in the shock at all.
Wow!
Absorption.
That's what NASA is all about.
Even if two people jumped, it would be fine.
Well, then...
Watch out!
Ha-ha-ha!
But he's jumping out of consideration.
That's sweet.
A little bit considerate.
He's just a little bit crunched up.
Just in time.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.I'm sorry.
It is possible for two normal people to do it.
The other characteristic is that when the partner gets into the root, he/she can leave the root without noticing it.
I see. I see.
Okay, let's talk about the pillow I was interested in earlier.
May I?
It's really good.
What's that?
It gets me even closer to zero-gravity sleep.
What?
What, what, what, what?
It's going up!
What? Why are your legs up?
My leg! My leg, uh!
What?
They're going up, they're going up.
Some women do it to reduce swelling.
Some do it with a futon or a pillow.
But we can do it with a machine.
It's also possible to raise the upper body.
Wow!
It's like a slap.
It's not like a sandwich.
That's as far as I got, yes.
Isn't this kind of hard to sleep in at first glance?
This, this is really good.
It's great.
It's great. - No, it's not.
No, it's not.
It keeps you relaxed.
We let you rest.
If you have a sore back...
If you have a sore back, you could not lie on your back with this fever, but now you can.
I don't want to talk about what I said earlier, but...
You're doing a good job.
You're doing great.Great job.
Now we'll get to the part about getting the blood flowing even better.
Now the vibrations.
I'm surprised. I thought you'd be a little more confident.
I didn't tell you.
Oh, this is good? For your body.
I've been known to get drowsy on buses and trains.
The irregular shaking of the train
It's supposed to make you sleepy.
This looks expensive.
This is expensive, by the way.
By the way, this one is a double size
It costs 858,000 yen.
850,000 yen!
That's expensive!
But even if you say so...
I don't think it's too much.
The features...
Amazing.
What's more...
This bed...
When it detects snoring, it moves up 12 degrees.
When you snore.
When you snore, it moves up 12 degrees and vibrates to wake you up.
It also has a function to wake you up.
Can I pretend to snore?
It's very smart.
You have to be very good at it to wake it up.
It doesn't respond.
That's right.
The vibrations have to be transmitted together.
Like a snoring gar, it has to vibrate.
It's designed not to respond.
You're a good snorer.
I'm a good snorer.
Just a little bit.Excuse me.
What's working?
The bed.
Excuse me.
Under here.
Under there?
Yes, sir.
Please, come and try one.
No, but I don't think so.
I gave it to you. In the first case, it was good.
I can't do it with a snore, can I?
If you write snoring, can you snore again?
I'm sorry.
I had to vibrate it a bit to get it to come.
I had to pull it and it went away.
Yeah.
It's good to be at this angle.
I like this angle.
I don't snore.
It's said to be a sleeping position that makes it harder to snore.
I mean, you should sleep in this position.
Is that wrong?
Yes, it is.
You can sleep in the 0G position as I mentioned earlier.
If you want to sleep straight today...
If you want to sleep straight today, you can do so by snoring.
It's up to you.
If you want to sleep like this from the beginning, you can do so.
If you want to sleep like this from the beginning, you can sleep in a position that prevents snoring.
Vibration... it's so cool!
If you don't notice the vibration...
If you don't notice the vibration, it will wake you up even stronger.
You never shrink the vibrator, do you?You definitely don't shrink a vibrator.
Vibration.
Excuse me, sir.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
It's totally fine to vibrate.
They keep calling it vibration.
Can I buy one of these?
If you find one you really like, please buy it.
I want to buy one.
The one you just bought.
The one you said you'd like.
I'll buy it.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
I really like you today.
That woman.
Woman.
In a world where girls work hard.
And playing music and so on.
And you two...
I don't know a single word about comedians.
Not a single character.
One millimeter.
I'm surprised.
I don't even know how to chat.
I don't know about chatting, but that's the part that transcends genres and stuff like that.
That's what I'm doing.
I thought it was cool when I bought it.
I was happy.
I'm glad.
So I'm gladSo let's just...
Let's do it somewhere.
Let's do something somewhere.
Let's do a show.
Let's start somewhere.
Did you have fun?
Mochi
I got a rice cake
As much as the shortest interlude.
How was it?
Sold
I'm glad to hear it.
You seem pleased.
How did it go?
Please.
Thanks.
That's all for you, Hakusui.
Thank you very much.
He said he had a feeling we could do something.
With you.